Neha Erasmus African Union High Level Implementation Panel Papers MS207
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1998 -- 2013; MS207.001; 1042 Digital Object(s)
  - Joint Technical Secretariat, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00437
    - Joint AEC/AUHIP/JTS Meeting 051210, 2010-12-05; MS207.001.00468
    - Joint Meeting of the Joint Technical Secretariat with the AUHIP and AEC, 2011-02-08; MS207.001.00469
    - NCP Delegation, 2011-02-27; MS207.001.00470
    - JTS Contact List, 2011-12-02; MS207.001.00471
  - Letters, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00472
    - Economic letters, 2011; MS207.001.00473
      - AUHIP letter to Abdel Gadir about Econ negotiations delay, 2011-02-08; MS207.001.00474
      - A letter to Abdel Gadir, 2011-02-10; MS207.001.00475
      - AUHIP letter to Amum, 2011-02-10; MS207.001.00476
      - Letter to participants in a conference, 2011-03-21; MS207.001.00477
      - A draft letter to Abdel Gadir, 2011-03-23; MS207.001.00478
      - A letter from AUHIP to Strauss-Kahn, 2011-04-03; MS207.001.00479
      - A letter from AUHIP to Strauss-Kahn, 2011-04-03; MS207.001.00480
      - A letter from the AUHIP to Zoellick, 2011-04-03; MS207.001.00481
      - A letter from the AUHIP to Zoellick, 2011-04-03; MS207.001.00482
      - AUHIP Letter to Abdel Gadir about Economic issues, 2011-05-25; MS207.001.00483
      - AUHIP Letter to NCP Economics, 2011-05-25; MS207.001.00484
      - AUHIP Letter to SPLM Economics, 2011-05-25; MS207.001.00485
    - For President Mbeki, 2011; MS207.001.00486
      - A draft letter from the AUHIP to Abdel Gadir and Amum among others, 2011-03-05; MS207.001.00487
      - A letter from Mbeki to Bashir, 2011-03-05; MS207.001.00488
      - Mbeki letter to the defense ministers of GoS and the Goss, 2011-03-05; MS207.001.00489
      - AUHIP draft invite VP Salva Kiir Abyei, 2011-03-05; MS207.001.00490
      - AUHIP draft letter VP Border Meeting, 2011-03-05; MS207.001.00491
    - Invitation letters, 2011; MS207.001.00492
      - An invitation letter from the AUHIP to Bashir, 2011-01-20; MS207.001.00493
      - An invitation letter from the AUHIP to Kiir, 2011-01-20; MS207.001.00494
      - Notes for the January 27, 2011 meeting in Khartoum, 2011-01-27; MS207.001.00495
    - Partners Meeting, 2012; MS207.001.00496
      - AUHIP Invite Chinese ambassador, 2012-01-23; MS207.001.00497
    - Letter to ADB 131210 - draft, 2010-12-13; MS207.001.00498
    - A letter from Abdul Mohammed to Paatii, 2010-12-21; MS207.001.00499
    - Letter to professors in Cambridge uni, 2011-01-11; MS207.001.00500
    - Letter visa Vladimir, 2011-01-23; MS207.001.00501
    - AUHIP Invite Amum, 2011-01-31; MS207.001.00502
    - Draft Econ Invite, 2011-01-31; MS207.001.00503
    - Letter visa Sarah Neha, 2011-01-31; MS207.001.00504
    - A letter from AUHIP to UNMIS/Menkerios - Invite Economic Talks, 2011-02-22; MS207.001.00505
    - A letter from AUHIP to US ambassador, 2011-02-22; MS207.001.00506
    - Letter to IGAD 200311, 2011-03-20; MS207.001.00507
    - Letter to IGAD 200311, 2011-03-20; MS207.001.00508
    - Letter from the AUHIP to Humanity United 290311, 2011-03-29; MS207.001.00509
    - Letter from AUHIP to Humanity United 290311, 2011-03-29; MS207.001.00510
    - Letter to Okumu, AUBP, 2011-04-01; MS207.001.00511
    - Letter to Okumu, AUBP, 2011-04-01; MS207.001.00512
    - A draft letter to Kiir, 2011-04-01; MS207.001.00513
    - Letter to IGAD 280411, 2011-04-28; MS207.001.00514
    - Letter to IGAD 280411, 2011-04-28; MS207.001.00515
    - Letter from AUHIP to Bashir, 2011-05-03; MS207.001.00516
    - Letter from the AUHIP to Pol Com NCP, 2011-05-04; MS207.001.00517
    - Letter from the AUHIP to Pol Com SPLM - draft, 2011-05-04; MS207.001.00518
    - Letter from the AUHIP to Pol Com SPLM, 2011-05-04; MS207.001.00519
    - A letter to the SPLM Pol Com, 2011-05-05; MS207.001.00520
    - A letter to Security cluster group invite NCP, 2011-05-10; MS207.001.00521
    - A letter to Security cluster group invite NCP, 2011-05-10; MS207.001.00522
    - A letter to Security cluster group invite SPLM, 2011-05-10; MS207.001.00523
    - A letter to Security cluster group invite SPLM, 2011-05-10; MS207.001.00524
    - Invitation Econ 19-21 May NCP, 2011-05-11; MS207.001.00525
    - Invitation Econ 19-21 May SPLM, 2011-05-11; MS207.001.00526
    - Letter to IGAD 140511, 2011-05-14; MS207.001.00527
    - AUHIP Letter to UNECA, 2011-05-24; MS207.001.00528
    - AUHIP letter to Abdoulie Janneh - United Nations Economic Commission for Africa, 2011-05-24; MS207.001.00529
    - AUHIP Letter Abdel Gadir, 2011-05-25; MS207.001.00530
    - A letter to Mbeki, 2011-05-25; MS207.001.00531
    - AUHIP Letter to NCP, 2011-05-31; MS207.001.00532
    - letter to Idriss on Citizenship, 2011-05-31; MS207.001.00533
    - AUHIP Letter Amum, 2011-06-01; MS207.001.00534
    - AUHIP Letter Legal ClusterAbdel Gadir, 2011-06-01; MS207.001.00535
    - AUHIP Letter Legal Cluster Amum, 2011-06-01; MS207.001.00536
    - Letter for AUBP Assistance, 2011-06-01; MS207.001.00537
    - Request for AUBP Assistance, 2011-06-01; MS207.001.00538
    - Letter from the AUHIP on Immigration, 2011-06-02; MS207.001.00539
    - Letter from AUHIP to Amum about Final Negotiations, 2011-06-06; MS207.001.00540
    - Letter from the AUHIP to Abdelgadir about Final Negotiations, 2011-06-06; MS207.001.00541
    - Letter from AUHIP about Final Negotiations to SPLM, 2011-06-06; MS207.001.00542
    - AUHIP Letter Abyei Abdel Gadir, 2011-06-30; MS207.001.00543
    - AUHIP Letter Abdel Gadir, 2011-06-30; MS207.001.00544
    - AUHIP Letter Abyei Amum, 2011-06-30; MS207.001.00545
    - Letter asking for visa to Laura James, 2011-07-03; MS207.001.00546
    - AUHIP Letter Plumbly Assessment and Evaluation Commission, 2011-07-09; MS207.001.00547
    - letter to Sir Derek - Assessment and Evaluation Commission, 2011-07-09; MS207.001.00548
    - A letter from Abdul Mohammed to Gambari, 2011-07-12; MS207.001.00549
    - AUHIP Letter to Gambari, 2011-07-12; MS207.001.00550
    - AUHIP Letter to Tufts WPF, 2011-07-12; MS207.001.00551
    - AUHIP Letter to Tufts WPF, 2011-07-12; MS207.001.00552
    - A letter from Mbeki to Bashir, 2011-07-14; MS207.001.00553
    - Abdl Mohammed Letter to IGAD Staff Recruitment, 2011-07-16; MS207.001.00554
    - Abdl Mohammed Letter to IGAD Staff Recruitment, 2011-07-16; MS207.001.00555
    - Letter asking for visa to Neha, 2011-07-18; MS207.001.00556
    - AUHIP JC invite Abdel Gadir, 2011-07-21; MS207.001.00557
    - AUHIP JC invite Amum, 2011-07-21; MS207.001.00558
    - JC JPSM invite GoS, 2011-07-21; MS207.001.00559
    - JC JPSM invite RoSS, 2011-07-21; MS207.001.00560
    - GoSS - Akec letter on Abyei to Mbeki, 2011-07-27; MS207.001.00561
    - AUHIP Econ Invite Abdel Gadir, 2011-07-28; MS207.001.00562
    - AUHIP Invite Abdel Gadir, 2011-07-28; MS207.001.00563
    - AUHIP Invite Amum, 2011-07-28; MS207.001.00564
    - AUHIP Invite Amum, 2011-07-28; MS207.001.00565
    - AUHIP Letter UNSG, 2011-07-30; MS207.001.00566
    - Letter visa Laura, 2011-07-31; MS207.001.00567
    - AUHIP letter Siddig - Sudan Minister of Finance, 2011-08-02; MS207.001.00568
    - AUHIP letter Siddig - Sudan Minister of Finance, 2011-08-02; MS207.001.00569
    - AUHIP letter Amum, 2011-08-02; MS207.001.00570
    - AUHIP Letter RoSS, 2011-08-05; MS207.001.00571
    - AUHIP Letter UNISFA, 2011-08-06; MS207.001.00572
    - AUHIP Letter Abdel Gadir, 2011-08-06; MS207.001.00573
    - AUHIP Letter Amum, 2011-08-06; MS207.001.00574
    - AUHIP Letter Amum, 2011-08-06; MS207.001.00575
    - AUHIP Letter Abyei Committee Abdel Gadir, 2011-08-09; MS207.001.00576
    - AbdulMohammed Memo Copying, 2011-08-11; MS207.001.00577
    - AUHIP Letter Kaberuka - Africa development bank, 2011-08-15; MS207.001.00578
    - AUHIP Letter to the IMF, 2011-08-15; MS207.001.00579
    - AUHIP Letter Sept Negotiations, 2011-08-18; MS207.001.00580
    - AUHIP letter Abdel Gadir, 2011-08-25; MS207.001.00581
    - AUHIP letter Abdel Gadir, 2011-08-25; MS207.001.00582
    - AUHIP letter Amum, 2011-08-25; MS207.001.00583
    - AUHIP letter Amum, 2011-08-25; MS207.001.00584
    - AUHIP Invite Amum, 2011-08-26; MS207.001.00585
    - AUHIP Invite Ryder, 2011-08-26; MS207.001.00586
    - AUHIP Invite Partners Gujin, 2011-08-26; MS207.001.00587
    - AUHIP Invite Partners Stiansen, 2011-08-27; MS207.001.00588
    - AUHIP Invite Partners Guijin, 2011-08-27; MS207.001.00589
    - AUHIP Invite Ryder, 2011-08-27; MS207.001.00590
    - AUHIP Invite Menkerios, 2011-08-27; MS207.001.00591
    - AUHIP Invite Princeton Lyman, 2011-08-27; MS207.001.00592
    - AUHIP letter Abyei FC UNISFA, 2011-08-27; MS207.001.00593
    - AUHIP Letter Sep GoS, 2011-08-27; MS207.001.00594
    - AUHIP Letter Sep GoSS, 2011-08-27; MS207.001.00595
    - AUHIP Letter Sep GoSS, 2011-08-27; MS207.001.00596
    - AUHIP letter Abyei FC UNISFA, 2011-08-28; MS207.001.00597
    - AUHIP letter Mukhtar lead negotiator, 2011-09-09; MS207.001.00598
    - AUHIP letter Mukhtar lead negotiator, 2011-09-09; MS207.001.00599
    - AUHIP letter Mukhtar lead negotiator, 2011-09-09; MS207.001.00600
    - AUHIP letter Pres Bashir, 2011-09-14; MS207.001.00601
    - AUHIP letter Pres Bashir, 2011-09-14; MS207.001.00602
    - AUHIP letter Pres Kiir, 2011-09-14; MS207.001.00603
    - A letter from Amum to Mbeki, 2011-09-17; MS207.001.00604
    - GoS - Abdel Gadir Reponse to Mbeki, 2011-09-26; MS207.001.00605
    - Abdel Gadir Reponse to Aide Memore NS Borders, 2011-09-26; MS207.001.00606
    - Invitation Letter Econ Meeting, 2011-10-05; MS207.001.00607
    - AUHIP Letter to professors in Cambridge, 2011-10-11; MS207.001.00608
    - AUHIP Invite Abdel Gadir, 2011-11-02; MS207.001.00609
    - AUHIP Invite Amum, 2011-11-02; MS207.001.00610
    - Letter to IGAD - draft, 2011-11-02; MS207.001.00611
    - Letter to ADB 071111 - draft, 2011-11-07; MS207.001.00612
    - Letter to ADB 071111, 2011-11-07; MS207.001.00613
    - Letter to IGAD 071111, 2011-11-07; MS207.001.00614
    - AUHIP Invite Amum, 2011-11-08; MS207.001.00615
    - AUHIP Invite Abdel Gadir, 2011-11-08; MS207.001.00616
    - Letter to IGAD 131111, 2011-11-13; MS207.001.00617
    - AUHIP invitation to RoSS, 2011-11-23; MS207.001.00618
    - AUHIP invitation to RoSS, 2011-11-23; MS207.001.00619
    - Letter visa Paattii, 2011-12-06; MS207.001.00620
    - Letter visa Paattii, 2011-12-06; MS207.001.00621
    - AUHIP invite arrears Amum, 2011-12-07; MS207.001.00622
    - AUHIP invite arrears Amum, 2011-12-07; MS207.001.00623
    - AUHIP invite arrears Abdel Gadir, 2011-12-07; MS207.001.00624
    - AUHIP invite arrears Abdel Gadir, 2011-12-07; MS207.001.00625
    - AUHIP Letter Norway ambassador, 2012-01-25; MS207.001.00626
    - AUHIP Letter Norway ambassador, 2012-01-25; MS207.001.00627
    - A draft letter by Thabo Mbeki to al Bashir, 2012-02-02; MS207.001.00628
    - AUHIP Draft Letter to Presidents JPSM, 2012-02-17; MS207.001.00629
    - AUHIP invite FC UNISFA, 2012-03-02; MS207.001.00630
    - AUHIP invite FC UNISFA, 2012-03-02; MS207.001.00631
    - A letter from Kiir to Mbeki, 2012-03-20; MS207.001.00632
    - A draft letter from Abdul Mohammed, 2012-04-09; MS207.001.00633
    - A letter from Abdul Mohammed to Paatii, 2012-04-09; MS207.001.00634
    - Abdl Mohammed letter to Princeton Lyman, 2012-04-22; MS207.001.00635
    - Abdul Mohammed letter to Thabo Mbeki, 2012-04-22; MS207.001.00636
  - Meetings, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00637
    - Conferences, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00638
      - A letter to the African Union Conference facilities, 2010-09-13; MS207.001.00639
      - Concept Paper on Convening a Symposium on the Year of Peace and Security, 2010-09-13; MS207.001.00640
      - High-Level Meeting on Sudan in the Margins of the AU Summit, 2011-01-25; MS207.001.00641
      - A draft - AU Assembly of Heads of State and Government, 2011-01-26; MS207.001.00642
    - Internal Meetings, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00643
      - Agenda internal meeting agenda181010, 2010-10-18; MS207.001.00644
      - Agenda for Internal Meeting 20th October 2010, 2010-10-20; MS207.001.00645
      - Internal Meeting 201010, 2010-10-20; MS207.001.00646
      - Internal Meeting 211010, 2010-10-21; MS207.001.00647
      - Internal Meeting 231010, 2010-10-23; MS207.001.00648
      - Internal Meeting 241010, 2010-10-24; MS207.001.00649
      - Internal Meeting 251010, 2010-10-25; MS207.001.00650
      - Internal Meeting 271010, 2010-10-27; MS207.001.00651
      - Internal Meeting 301010, 2010-10-30; MS207.001.00652
      - Internal Meeting 311010, 2010-10-31; MS207.001.00653
      - Internal Meeting 121110, 2010-11-12; MS207.001.00654
      - Agenda Internal Meeting 021210, 2010-12-02; MS207.001.00655
      - Internal Meeting 021210, 2010-12-02; MS207.001.00656
      - Internal Meeting 031210, 2010-12-03; MS207.001.00657
      - Internal Meeting 151210, 2010-12-15; MS207.001.00658
      - Internal Meeting 161210, 2010-12-16; MS207.001.00659
      - Internal meeting 100111, 2011-01-10; MS207.001.00660
      - Action Points from Internal AUHIP Meeting, 2011-01-21; MS207.001.00661
      - Agenda Internal AUHIP Meeting 1 February 2011, 2011-02-01; MS207.001.00662
      - Internal Meeting 010211, 2011-02-01; MS207.001.00663
      - Internal Meeting 020211, 2011-02-02; MS207.001.00664
      - Internal Meeting Agenda 160311, 2011-03-16; MS207.001.00665
      - Internal Meeting 180311, 2011-03-18; MS207.001.00666
      - Staff Internal Meeting 180311, 2011-03-18; MS207.001.00667
      - Staff Internal Meeting 190311, 2011-03-19; MS207.001.00668
      - Internal Meeting 200311, 2011-03-20; MS207.001.00669
      - Internal Meeting Action Points 220311, 2011-03-22; MS207.001.00670
      - Internal Meeting Agenda 220311, 2011-03-22; MS207.001.00671
      - Internal Meeting 230311, 2011-03-23; MS207.001.00672
      - Internal Meeting Action Points 050411, 2011-04-05; MS207.001.00673
      - Internal Meeting Agenda 050411 AM, 2011-04-05; MS207.001.00674
      - Internal Meeting Agenda 050411, 2011-04-05; MS207.001.00675
      - Internal Meeting Darfur 050411, 2011-04-05; MS207.001.00676
      - Internal Meeting 040511, 2011-05-04; MS207.001.00677
      - Internal Meeting 070611, 2011-06-07; MS207.001.00678
      - Internal AUHIP Meeting Agenda 201011, 2011-10-20; MS207.001.00679
      - Internal Meeting 221011, 2011-10-22; MS207.001.00680
      - Agenda Internal AUHIP Meeting 311011, 2011-10-30; MS207.001.00681
    - Presidency meeting, 2011; MS207.001.00682
      - Specific Commitments on Citizenship and Residency, 2011-01-21; MS207.001.00683
      - Instructions to the Teams Negotiating Post-Referendum Issues on Citizenship and Related Matters, 2011-01-21; MS207.001.00684
      - Detailed Talking Points for Meeting with Presidents Bashir and Kiir, 2011-01-23; MS207.001.00685
      - Detailed Talking Points for Meeting with Presidents Bashir and Kiir on Borders, 2011-01-25; MS207.001.00686
      - Detailed Talking Points for Meeting with Presidents Bashir and Kiir, 27 January 2011, 2011-01-25; MS207.001.00687
      - Notes on meeting in Khartoum, 2011-01-27; MS207.001.00688
      - Mbeki invite to Bashir, 2011-01-27; MS207.001.00689
    - Washington Trip, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00690
      - Letters to Creditors, 2011; MS207.001.00691
        - Note Verbale to Austria 120411, 2011-04-12; MS207.001.00692
        - Note Verbale to Belgium 120411, 2011-04-12; MS207.001.00693
        - Note Verbale to China, 2011-04-12; MS207.001.00694
        - Note Verbale to Denmark, 2011-04-12; MS207.001.00695
        - Note Verbale to Kuwait, 2011-04-12; MS207.001.00696
        - Note Verbale to Saudi Arabia, 2011-04-12; MS207.001.00697
      - Photos, 2010 -- 2011; MS207.001.00698
        - Abdul Mohammed picture, 2010-09-13; MS207.001.00699
        - Adamu Abubaker picture, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00700
        - Ben Leo picture, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00701
        - Laura James picture, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00702
        - Sani Atsu picture, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00703
      - Visit of AU High Implementation Panel Presidents Mbeki, Buyoya, Abubaker Washington, DC, April 14-19, 2011, 2011-04-13; MS207.001.00704; Erasmus, Neha
      - Schedule of Meetings in Washington, 2011-04-13; MS207.001.00705
      - AUHIP Delegation Members - Clearance Information, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00706
      - AUHIP Schedule Washington, DC, April 14-19, 2011 - draft, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00707
      - AUHIP Schedule Washington, DC, April 14-19, 2011 - draft, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00708
      - AUHIP Schedule Washington, DC, April 14-19, 2011 - draft, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00709
      - AUHIP Schedule Washington, DC, April 14-19, 2011 - draft, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00710
      - AUHIP Schedule Washington, DC, April 14-19, 2011 - apr 15, 2011-04-14; MS207.001.00711
      - Agenda Internal Meeting 150411, 2011-04-15; MS207.001.00712
      - Agenda Internal Meeting 150411 - draft, 2011-04-15; MS207.001.00713
      - Meeting with SPLM, 2011-04-15; MS207.001.00714
      - AUHIP Schedule Washington, DC, April 14-19, 2011 - draft, 2011-04-16; MS207.001.00715
      - AUHIP Schedule Washington, DC, April 14-19, 2011 - draft, 2011-04-17; MS207.001.00716
      - AUHIP Schedule Washington, DC, April 14-19, 2011 - draft, 2011-04-17; MS207.001.00717
      - Talking Points on Economic Issues: Meeting with Vice President Biden, 2011-04-18; MS207.001.00718
      - World Bank Talking Points - Additional Points for Meeting with World Bank President, 2011-04-18; MS207.001.00719
    - Meeting ad hoc boundary commission - notes, 2010-05-11; MS207.001.00720
    - Meeting notes Border committee, 2010-08-08; MS207.001.00721
    - Meeting with UNIRED, 2010-08-16; MS207.001.00722
    - Meeting between the Panel and the Parties, 2010-08-30; MS207.001.00723
    - Meeting with US ambassador, 2010-08-30; MS207.001.00724
    - Meeting President Mbeki and FVP Salva Kiir 31 Aug 2010, 2010-08-31; MS207.001.00725
    - Meeting with Concordis, 2010-09-05; MS207.001.00726
    - Meetings with Sudan Council of Churches on the South South Dialogue, 2010-09-07; MS207.001.00727
    - Assessment and Evaluation Commission, 2010-09-20; MS207.001.00728
    - Meeting on Contingency Planning for Sudan, 2010-10-01; MS207.001.00729
    - Meeting with UN, 2010-10-23; MS207.001.00730
    - Meeting with SPLM Political Committee, 2010-10-26; MS207.001.00731
    - Meeting with Misiriya Leadership, 2010-10-27; MS207.001.00732
    - Meeting Yasir Arman - SPLM Northern Sector HQ, Khartoum, 2010-10-28; MS207.001.00733
    - Meeting with Gen. Scott Gration, 2010-10-29; MS207.001.00734
    - Meeting Baroness Valerie Amos 091110, 2010-11-09; MS207.001.00735
    - Report on Meeting with Border Committee Chair 130111, 2011-01-13; MS207.001.00736
    - Meeting on Border Symposium with UK, UNMIS & Concordis 240111, 2011-01-24; MS207.001.00737
    - Meeting with Border Committee Chair and Deputy, 2011-02-02; MS207.001.00738
    - Metting with UNSC, 2011-05-22; MS207.001.00739
    - Security Meeting - Brainstorming, 2011-05-25 -- 2011-05-26; MS207.001.00740
    - Draft IGAD Communique - Intergovernmental Authority on Development, 2011-07-03; MS207.001.00741
    - Meetings with GoSS / SPLM Economic Team, 2011-08-29; MS207.001.00742
    - Meeting with General Salva Mathok, 1 Sep 2011, 2011-09-01; MS207.001.00743
    - Meeting with Kenya Minister of Energy and Public Works, 2012-01-13; MS207.001.00744
    - Meeting with CNPC 14 May 2012, 2012-05-14; MS207.001.00745
  - Papers, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00746
    - Briefing papers, 2010 -- 2012; MS207.001.00747
      - Panel Visit, 2010; MS207.001.00748
        - Briefing papers AEC, 2010; MS207.001.00749
          - Briefing Papers PRI AEC, 2010-10-18; MS207.001.00750
        - Briefing papers AUHIP, 2010; MS207.001.00751
          - Briefing Paper Popular Consultations, 2010-10-17; MS207.001.00752; Erasmus, Neha
          - Briefing Paper South South Reconciliaton, 2010-10-17; MS207.001.00753; Erasmus, Neha
          - Briefing Paper Democratisation and Governance, 2010-10-18; MS207.001.00754; Erasmus, Neha
          - Briefing Paper US Support Package, 2010-10-18; MS207.001.00755; Lortan, Fiona
          - Briefing Paper Code of Conduct, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00756; Afako, Barney
        - Briefing papers UN, 2010; MS207.001.00757
          - Briefing Paper Abyei UN, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00758
          - Briefing Paper Referendum Preparations UN, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00759
          - UNMIS update briefing for the AUHIP, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00760
        - Final briefing papers, 2010; MS207.001.00761
          - Briefing Paper Abyei Final, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00762
          - Briefing Paper Borders Final, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00763
          - Briefing Paper Code of Conduct Final, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00764
          - Briefing Paper Democratisation and Governance Final, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00765
          - Briefing Paper Popular Consultations Final, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00766
          - Briefing Paper PRI AEC Final - AUHIP Briefing Paper on Post Referendum Negotiations, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00767
          - Briefing Paper Referendum UN AUHIP Final, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00768
          - Briefing Paper Security UNMIS Final, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00769
          - Final Briefing Paper South South Reconciliaton, 2010-10-19; MS207.001.00770
        - Briefing Plan, 2010-10-16; MS207.001.00771
        - AUHIP Background Papers Panel Visit, 2010-10-17; MS207.001.00772
        - Briefing Papers Plan, 2010-10-17; MS207.001.00773
        - Requested Background Papers Panel Visit, 2010-10-17; MS207.001.00774
      - Update on the status of the post-referendum negotiation cluster meetings, 2010-09-20; MS207.001.00775
      - Briefing on AUHIP October 2011 Visit to Sudan and South Sudan, 2011-10; MS207.001.00776
      - Meetings in Khartoum between Presidents Kiir and Bashir - Preliminary Update and Reflections, 2011-10-11; MS207.001.00777
      - Talking Points for Juba Trip - General Salva Mathok, Deputy Minister for Interior, 2011-10-14; MS207.001.00778
      - Note on the Second Meeting of the JPSM, 2011-10-19; MS207.001.00779
      - Area of Operations of the SDBZ, 2011-10-26; MS207.001.00780
      - South Sudan, 2012-03-08; MS207.001.00781
    - Statements, 2011; MS207.001.00782
      - Troika Statement on Negotiations between Sudan and South Sudan - Draft, 2011-11; MS207.001.00783
    - Matrix of the Recommendations of the First and Second Symposiums of the Intermixture States, 2010-08-24; MS207.001.00784
    - Tamazuj Border - concept note Draft 2, 2010-08-27; MS207.001.00785
    - Tamazuj border powerpoint presentation, 2010-08-27; MS207.001.00786
    - Ideas and Conepts for Abyei, 2010-08-31; MS207.001.00787
    - Defining the North South Border, 2010-09-02; MS207.001.00788; International Crisis Group
      Abyei (Sudan); Heglig (Sudan); Darfur (Sudan); Kurdufān al-Janūbīyah (Sudan); Northern Bahr el Ghazal State (South Sudan); Upper Nile State (South Sudan); Borderlands; Boundary disputes; Border security; Petroleum industry and trade; Oil fields; Dinka (African people); Misirié (Arab tribe); Sudan--Politics and government; South Sudan--Politics and government--2011-; Comprehensive Peace Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement, Sudan People's Liberation Army (2005); Political issues; Kafia Kingi (African people); International Crisis Group; Sudan People's Liberation Movement; Sudan People's Liberation Army; National Congress Party
    - AUHIP year end PSC Report - Draft 1, 2010-09-07; MS207.001.00789
    - Why Sudan's Popular Consultation Matters, Jason Gluck, USIP, 2010-09-08; MS207.001.00790
    - Sudan Update to African Union - Update on Recent Events and Dynamics in Sudan - Draft, 2010-10-07; MS207.001.00791